getusefulinfo.com 2012-11-02

# Privacy

###  Privacy Policy

Getusefulinfo.com Privacy Policy describes how we maintain your personal information when you register for Getusefulinfo.com’s services.

###  Personal information

  * You will need to create an Account to use the services on Getusefulinfo.com. Getusefulinfo.com will collect personal information when you create your Account which includes your email address, your name and a password, which is used to protect your account from unauthorized access.
  * As a member, you can create a profile which includes personal information, such as your name (if no nickname is set), gender, location and also add profile photo. This information may be accessed and viewed by other members.
  * When you invite new members into your network or send messages, Getusefulinfo.com collects and maintains the email addresses associated with the messages.

###  Uses and Information Sharing

  * Your profile information displayed includes your name (if no nickname is set), gender, location and date of joining.
  * When you send messages, your name and email address will be identified in the message. We also use your name and email address to notify you of new members, messages and or other information, such as invitations to join, new alerts including ratings, reviews, recommendations, and crush notices.
  * If you invite another person or friends to join, we use the name and email address you provide us to contact that person and, if necessary, may send reminders to join.
  * Friends or other persons can search your profile by using the nickname provided in your profile.
  * Users may also post reviews, comments, polls, quizzes, so long as the contents are not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and not contain political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam".
  * Getusefulinfo.com pre-screens user submitted polls & quizzes, the right to approve, reject or remove such content solely remains with Getusefulinfo.com
  * You agree not to submit material that is copyrighted, protected by trade secret or otherwise subject to third party proprietary rights, including privacy and publicity rights, unless you are the owner of such rights.

###  Disclaimer

We value the privacy of information pertaining to its associates. We do not use or disclose information about your individual visits to our portal.

We will not use information about you without your permission and will provide the means for you to manage and control the information that you have provided. You agree to receive promotional communications from us (email and/or SMS) unless you specifically indicate otherwise in writing to us.

We do not disclose any personal information to advertisers and for other marketing and promotional purposes that could be used to personally identify you, such as your password, credit card number and bank account number.
